http://www.mountainbikingasia.com/links-for-you/privacy/

Articles/News
F.A.Q.
I want your tour updates!
Book Now or Indicate Interest
China Castle House Cycling!
Hong Kong Cycling
Trips for One or Two
Hike the Wild Wall of China!
A Private Tour Cycling Hong Kongs Wild Side for Two!
A Private tour Cycling Chinas Castle Houses for two!
Mountainbiking the Backroads of Tibet!
Mongolia!
Ride a Bamboo Bike through Tibetan Villages!
Borneo Island, Malaysia
Family Adventures!
privacyJanuary 13, 2016Privacy Policy
All information gathered through our booking process and payment process from any client is protected on a secure server. Excel sheets or other types of documents received through group organizers or schools are deleted from our email and all printed copies are shredded in a reasonable time frame after tour completion. No information will be shared in any form with any other marketing organizations.
Passport Numbers, Passport names, Gender, Date of Birth, Expiries, Nationalities, Emergency contacts will be shared with travel operators, airlines, ticketing agencies, hotels, insurance and Government agencies as required for operation of tour. These entities have their own privacy policies and to our knowledge conform to similar guidelines as ours. We will not take responsibility for these entities upkeep of their own privacy policies.
Emails will be used for Mountainbikingasia.com own marketing purposes. Unsubscibe options are available for recipient action.
Photographs, sound bytes and video clips of clients may be used in our website, facebook and email marketing. We will not identify any participants names with posted media when under our decision. We will not take responsibility for third party posts.
Written notice is needed for any objection. Written objections can come in the form of email , letter or fax and must state specifically the location of the objectionable media, a screenshot identification and when posted (in the case of facebook or other social media). Upon receipt we will make every effort to delete or modify questioned media.   The objection must be made by the person in the media and this will be verified.
×
Want more information about this tour?
Get email alerts about tour dates you are interested in
and
Number of people in your group Interested in this tour:
Sign me up for the Mountain biking asia newsletter to keep me up to date
on all upcoming cycling tours! (To complete the sign up to our newsletter, please enter Capcha text and hit "Submit" in resulting popup).
*We will only email you about upcoming tours you are interested in
and you may opt out at anytime. We will never sell your personal
information to advertisers or spammers. Privacy Policy
Close
Save And See Dates
×
Interested in this tour but not quite sure? Planning a trip
sometime in the future? Select a date of interest and we
will e-mail you when the tour date is approaching so you will
have plenty of time to book. You may select several dates.
This Tour Start Daily Every:
Select a date to see tour information:
Selected Tour Date:
Needed to Confirm this Tour Date:
Confirm in Advance:
People Interested:
People Booked:
This tour is confirmed. Book Now!
Tours you are Interested in
Tour Date
Not Interested?
Done signing up for tour info? Go back to the tour page:
Close
×
Dates and Prices
Privacy Policy
All information gathered through our booking process and payment process from any client is protected on a secure server. Excel sheets or other types of documents received through group organizers or schools are deleted from our email and all printed copies are shredded in a reasonable time frame after tour completion. No information will be shared in any form with any other marketing organizations.
Passport Numbers, Passport names, Gender, Date of Birth, Expiries, Nationalities, Emergency contacts will be shared with travel operators, airlines, ticketing agencies, hotels, insurance and Government agencies as required for operation of tour. These entities have their own privacy policies and to our knowledge conform to similar guidelines as ours. We will not take responsibility for these entities upkeep of their own privacy policies.
Emails will be used for Mountainbikingasia.com own marketing purposes. Unsubscibe options are available for recipient action.
Photographs, sound bytes and video clips of clients may be used in our website, facebook and email marketing. We will not identify any participants names with posted media when under our decision. We will not take responsibility for third party posts.
Written notice is needed for any objection. Written objections can come in the form of email , letter or fax and must state specifically the location of the objectionable media, a screenshot identification and when posted (in the case of facebook or other social media). Upon receipt we will make every effort to delete or modify questioned media.   The objection must be made by the person in the media and this will be verified.
Close
×
Trip Suitability
Privacy Policy
All information gathered through our booking process and payment process from any client is protected on a secure server. Excel sheets or other types of documents received through group organizers or schools are deleted from our email and all printed copies are shredded in a reasonable time frame after tour completion. No information will be shared in any form with any other marketing organizations.
Passport Numbers, Passport names, Gender, Date of Birth, Expiries, Nationalities, Emergency contacts will be shared with travel operators, airlines, ticketing agencies, hotels, insurance and Government agencies as required for operation of tour. These entities have their own privacy policies and to our knowledge conform to similar guidelines as ours. We will not take responsibility for these entities upkeep of their own privacy policies.
Emails will be used for Mountainbikingasia.com own marketing purposes. Unsubscibe options are available for recipient action.
Photographs, sound bytes and video clips of clients may be used in our website, facebook and email marketing. We will not identify any participants names with posted media when under our decision. We will not take responsibility for third party posts.
Written notice is needed for any objection. Written objections can come in the form of email , letter or fax and must state specifically the location of the objectionable media, a screenshot identification and when posted (in the case of facebook or other social media). Upon receipt we will make every effort to delete or modify questioned media.   The objection must be made by the person in the media and this will be verified.
Close
×
Meet and Depart
Privacy Policy
All information gathered through our booking process and payment process from any client is protected on a secure server. Excel sheets or other types of documents received through group organizers or schools are deleted from our email and all printed copies are shredded in a reasonable time frame after tour completion. No information will be shared in any form with any other marketing organizations.
Passport Numbers, Passport names, Gender, Date of Birth, Expiries, Nationalities, Emergency contacts will be shared with travel operators, airlines, ticketing agencies, hotels, insurance and Government agencies as required for operation of tour. These entities have their own privacy policies and to our knowledge conform to similar guidelines as ours. We will not take responsibility for these entities upkeep of their own privacy policies.
Emails will be used for Mountainbikingasia.com own marketing purposes. Unsubscibe options are available for recipient action.
Photographs, sound bytes and video clips of clients may be used in our website, facebook and email marketing. We will not identify any participants names with posted media when under our decision. We will not take responsibility for third party posts.
Written notice is needed for any objection. Written objections can come in the form of email , letter or fax and must state specifically the location of the objectionable media, a screenshot identification and when posted (in the case of facebook or other social media). Upon receipt we will make every effort to delete or modify questioned media.   The objection must be made by the person in the media and this will be verified.
Close
